neverland-motor.com 2012-10-30

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Neverland-motor.com (hereinafter referred to as "we" or “Site” )  is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. We surely bear it in mind that the customers are everything for us. We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties at any time. Your data is only used to process orders and for marketing. By using Neverland-motor.com or by purchasing products or services from us, you agree to be bound by this policy, so please take your time to read this policy.

What kind of information does Neverland-motor.com collect from the customers?

1\. Information you provided us: We receive and store information when you enter on Neverland-motor.com, or give us in any other way. You can choose not to supply us with certain kinds of information. We only use your information to improve our products and services as well as to help us administer our Site.  
2\. Information we collect by automated means: We also automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us for example when you visit our Sites. Like many other Sites we use cookies. We will receive some information when you browse our Sites.  
3\. From other sources: We might also receive information about you from other sources, such as in providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, and we may add that information to our account information.

Does Neverland-motor.com share your information with others？

We will not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties unless you have requested or authorized us to do so. We share your information only in accordance with Privacy Policy as follows:

**Neverland-motor.com business partners:**  We cooperate closely with our affiliated business partners.   
We may share your information with our business partners who join us in online promotion, who provide us with products or service, and who run Sites linked to ours. You will be able to know when a third party is involved.

**Third-party service providers:**  We employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. For example: to deliver parcels, to send mails or emails, to analyze data, to assist with marketing, to provide search results and links (including paid search results and links), to deal with the payment and to provide service to the customers. They can access the data they need to fulfill their obligations, but abuse of the data for other purposes is prohibited.

**Third-party advertisers and links to other Sites:**  Our Site includes third-party advertisements and links to other Sites to whom we seldom provide identifiable customer data. However we have no way of controlling the cookies they might use or other particular functions. Moreover this Privacy Policy is not applicable to their usual practice.  
Promotion opportunities: Sometimes we offer promotion opportunities to the selected user groups of Neverland-motor.com Sites on behalf of other companies without their knowledge of your name and address.

**For the protection of Neverland-motor.com and other people:**  We may disclose personal information about our customers as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process. We may disclose information about you to protect against fraud and other crimes and to enforce our contracts with you. Obviously this does not violate this Privacy Policy in which we promise not to sell, rent out or share identifiable customer information for commercial benefits.

How Neverland-motor.com uses Cookies?

Neverland-motor.com may use "cookies" to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Site stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. We may use cookies for some administrative purposes, for example, to store our customers' preferences for certain kinds of products or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our Site. The cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our customers via telephone, email, or any other means. If our customers are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they can set their browsers to refuse cookies. Certain of our services, however, could be dependent on cookies and our customers may disable those services by refusing cookies.

Comments, Reviews, and other Information

When using our Site you may have opportunities to post or submit comments, reviews, and other information to publicly accessible pages of our Site. When you post or submit such information it is done at your own risk, is made public, and is not subject to this policy.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

As we continue to develop our Site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, this Privacy Policy will be updated over time. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. Your continued access and use of our Sites will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy Policy. 

Suggestion and feedback

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [Service@neverland-motor.com](mailto:service@neverland-motor.com)
